The fish soup is here.
Sorry for the wait.
Here is your fish soup.
Let me serve you a bowl.
We'll do it ourselves.
Enjoy your meal.
How attentive.
Such a temper.
Are you still mad at me?
The fish soup is poisoned.
Could it be Mother's men?
It seems when we left the city gates,
we were still suspected.
The waiter is gone.
He's not from the inn.
Let's go back to the room first.
Since you've already found out
that the fish soup wasn't poisoned,
and only Her Ladyship's bowl was,
then the poisoner...
can only be you.
If I really wanted to kill her,
why would I save her from danger so many times?
Of course, it's for the ledger of the gold embezzlement case.
You failed to steal the ledger in the palace,
so you changed your identity,
followed us all the way,
and waited for an opportunity.
I just don't know
if you are General Shen's man,
or if there's someone else behind you.
Tell me.
What's going on?
Not again.
It was indeed me who stole the ledger in the palace,
but he was wrong about one thing.
I am indeed your cousin.
Otherwise,
with General Shen's wise and suspicious nature,
why would he trust me so much?
I just don't understand
why she would attack you.
Mr. Zhao,
don't dodge the main issue.
Who do you really work for?
Are you interrogating me?
Since Mr. Zhao wants to travel with Her Highness,
you should naturally treat us with sincerity.
I have no hidden agenda in following you.
My only purpose is to ensure your safety.
Although
I work for General Shen,
I don't want you to get hurt.
Even if you won't take my life,
dare you say
you haven't deceived me at all
and have no ulterior motives?
What motives could I have?
I saved your lives.
I paid for your expenses.
And I did all the fighting.
If I really have an ulterior motive,
I would hope
you could fall in love with me one day.
Does that count as a motive?
You
shouldn't have saved her.
She is an ungrateful wretch.
She was just betrayed by her closest kin.
It is right for her not to trust anyone.
Yeah.
You are so great.
Not only do you save the sweetheart who stabbed you,
but you also have to save your sweetheart's sweetheart.
Shut your mouth.
You like looking at me so much, cousin?
Robbery!
Stop! Robbery!
Put down your weapons
and surrender!
I advise you all
to behave.
Do you see my armor?
I belong to the Northern Army.
If you dare to make a move,
we will kill you all.
The Northern Army.
Baili Jinghong's men.
I wonder which general
you serve under
in the Northern Border Army.
You wouldn't know even if I told you.
The Jade-Faced Fierce General,
Young General Jiuying.
Have you heard of him?
Top-grade cloud brocade. You must be rich.
I advise you
to hand over all your silver immediately.
Otherwise... Humph.
What did the Second Boss eat?
The smell is too pungent.
Take them away.
The Second Boss is back.
Hurry, keep up.
Behave.
You rich people,
let's see how I deal with you.
Brother.
Second Brother.
Little sister.
Look, Boss.
I brought them back for you.
This batch is all rich people.
Brothers, uh,
take off their blindfolds.
Okay, let's see how these fat sheep look.
Boss, take a look.
How are they, Boss?
Not bad, right?
Yeah, this batch is not bad.
Take them inside.
Go.
Take them all.
Hehe.
Let me tell you, little sister.
As soon as I showed up,
the armor on my body,
they had never seen it before.
Really?
I was so majestic.
These weaklings from the city
were almost paralyzed on the spot.
You're really amazing, Second Brother.
Let me tell you.
These rich people have no experience.
They only have money.
We'll torture them well later. Mother.
Who are they?
Did the Boss rescue them too?
Why are they tied up?
Those brought back tied up are definitely not good people.
Don't look at them.
Careful, you might get beaten to death by them like your big brother.
Hurry inside.
Hurry.
Get in.
Hurry up.
Where is your general?
Behave and write a letter first.
Have someone come to ransom you.
If no one ransoms you,
we'll skin you alive.
I didn't expect the Northern Border Army to have such terrifying methods.
I haven't heard of this before.
Hmph.
Have some water first.
Oh, sister.
They haven't even paid yet.
Why are you being so polite to them?
Second Boss.
Please save my husband.
Dr. Zheng said
if we don't get money to buy medicine down the mountain,
he won't survive for three days.
Second Boss,
Miss Doukou,
please give me ten more copper coins to save his life.
Get up.
I beg you.
Hurry, get up.
My Huzi is still young.
He can't live without a father.
I kowtow to you. I beg you.
Please.
In pursuit of longevity,
the late emperor spent thousands of taels of silver just to eat a fish.
Escorting it all the way sacrificed many elite soldiers and fine horses.
What a sorrowful world.
I beg you, Second Boss.
Come.
Here, this is for you.
Get up.
It's not enough.
Well, I don't have any more either.
Thank you, Second Boss.
Thank you, Miss Doukou.
Go.
Hero,
aren't you under General Jiuying's command?
So shabby.
Giving so little money,
it's not even enough for a dose of medicine.
None of your business.
Mind your own business.
If no one comes to ransom you,
I will slaughter you all.
Do I still need to be ransomed?
I can give you gold right now.
What?
You have gold on you?
I don't have any on me right now.
But,
this mountain of yours actually has a
gold mine.
What?
A gold mine?
Hey, boss.
This kid says there's a gold mine on our mountain.
He's glib and looks like a gigolo.
Can we trust his words?
In our rundown Beimang Mountain,
could there really be a gold mine?
Don't you have the manpower?
You might as well give it a try.
Easy for you to say.
We have plenty of manpower.
But doesn't mining take a lot of effort?
Dig. If there isn't any,
I have plenty of strength and means.
What if there is?
Absolutely impossible.
I think you're just afraid we'll kill you,
and are making up lies to trick us.
He has a delicate face.
If we sell him to a male brothel,
the people there
will love a pretty boy like him.
Brother.
Look at this one, strong and sturdy.
Let's keep him to do the hard labor.
Well.
Leave this scholar for Doukou to be her husband.
He's the only one who looks like a good guy here.
Hey, brother.
What are you talking about?
Hey, sister.
Brother.
She's been shy since she was little. Don't you know?
Look at her. She's quite pretty.
What if we
sell her to the Hongxiu Brothel?
We can definitely make a lot of money.
If he does,
whip him.
You want to whip me?
I'll lay it on the line today.
If you can dig up a gold mine,
I'll twist my head off for you to kick like a ball.
Right here.
Are you kidding us in the middle of the night?
You aren't trying to run away, are you?
The Second Boss has extraordinary skills.
Where could I run?
What are you afraid of?
Glad you know your place.
I'll untie you.
You're playing dumb to take advantage of us.
Are you crazy?
It turned white instantly.
I've seen hair turn white overnight,
but never instantly like this.
He threw up blood just from touching the stone.
Could he be terminally ill and trying to scam us?
The gold mine is right here.
Start digging.
Boy.
Digging a mountain is no small task.
If you dare lie to me,
you'll walk into this stronghold
and be carried out dead.
Quick, go get someone.
Yes.
Let me.
Alright, you do it.
You're really strong, little sister.
Your stronghold
really is full of talents.
Oh, Boss.
Boss, look, there really is gold.
This is real gold, look.
Gold-finding technique.
You're from the Helian clan.
I hope you two chiefs can keep this a secret for me.
Don't worry.
We will keep our mouths shut.
Benefactor, I insulted you just now.
I'll twist my head off for you to kick like a ball.
Just kidding.
Wouldn't a bloody head
be creepy to kick?
The poison is acting up.
Boss, we're rich.
Haha.